http://www.workforcesafety.com/privacy-policy

Benefits & Services
Report Income Status (FL214)
File an Incident Report
Report Income Status (FL214)
myWSI
WorkersReporting an InjuryThe Claims ProcessAppeal an OrderBenefits & ServicesMedical Benefits Medical BenefitsWage-loss BenefitsPersonal Expenses ReimbursementReturn to Work ServicesPermanent Partial Impairment (PPI)Death Benefits Death BenefitsReport Income Status (FL214)FormsResourcesEmployersApply for CoverageSubmit Payroll ReportMake A PaymentRequest a QuoteInsurance Coverage InformationCoverage RequirementsRequest Premium QuoteCoverage TypesCoverage Limits & Rights of SubrogationManage Your AccountFailure to Secure CoverageVerification of Non-EmploymentPremium & Assessment InformationRequest Premium QuotePremium InformationAssessment InformationPayroll InformationPremium AuditReducing Your PremiumAcross State LinesExtraterritorial CoverageNorth Dakota Workers Working Out of StateReciprocal AgreementsAll States CoverageOut-of-State Employers Working in North DakotaOut-of-Country InjuriesOut-of-State Law Enforcement TrainingForms & ResourcesCommon QuestionsMedical ProvidersProvider RegistrationMedical TreatmentPharmacy ServicesFee ScheduleTreatment & Documentation PoliciesPrior AuthorizationBilling & PaymentFormsResourcesCommon QuestionsReturn to WorkNurse Case ManagementInjured Worker Assistance ProgramVocational Case ManagementRetrainingWork SearchPreferred Worker ProgramFormsResources Return to Work ResourcesCommon QuestionsSafetySafety TeamSafety Incentive ProgramsGrantsErgonomic Initiative GrantPrevious Grant Award RecipientsSTEP GrantEducationLearning Management SystemOSHA 10/30 Online Training ProgramSafety ServicesYoung Worker SafetyEventsSafety NewsForms & ResourcesQuick LinksClaim Lookup Claim LookupReport an InjuryFile an Incident ReportReport Income Status (FL214)Learning Management SystemQuick PaySubmit Payroll ReportComplete Verification of Non-Employment FormmyWSI
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Medium
GENERAL
GENERAL
Records received by North Dakota Workforce Safety & Insurance (WSI) from its website are subject to the same controls and uses as records collected by governmental offices visited in person and are open to the public upon request, unless otherwise specifically provided by law. WSI may be required to disclose collected information pursuant to a court order and may be required to share this information for other purposes authorized by law. If you have any questions about whether the information being provided will be released, upon request by a member of the public or otherwise, please contact us.
DOMAIN INFORMATION
DOMAIN INFORMATION
WSI uses website analytics tools to help measure how users access the website. WSI staff use the summary statistics gathered by these tools to review and measure usage, and makE enhancements to improve website performance and usability.
PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
This website is part of the State of North Dakota (State) computer system used to accomplish State functions. In order to protect information gathered, the State of North Dakota has security measures in place on this website including firewalls, encryption, and authenticated access to internal databases where needed. The State uses software programs to monitor this website for security purposes to ensure  it remains available to all users.
Credit card numbers collected through website applications are not stored or retained in any manner. The information is gathered and passed on through an intermediate software company, and a unique transaction number is returned and stored as proof of acceptance.
If you use this website to communicate with WSI and provide an email address, the email address is collected as a means to reply to you. WSI may forward your message to another agency or entity for appropriate action.
Cookies may be used under specific conditions. A cookie is a text file stored on your computer used to maintain an uninterrupted transaction with the application.
RETENTION OF INFORMATION
RETENTION OF INFORMATION
The information collected on this website is retained in accordance with the applicable Record Retention Schedules developed for WSI information.
DISCLAIMER
DISCLAIMER
In order to provide you with a wide variety of information about North Dakota, this site links to other websites maintained by individual state agencies, political subdivisions, nonprofit organizations, and private businesses. Each of these entities has the responsibility of setting their own privacy policy, and posting it on their websites. When you visit another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that website.
Although we try to keep the information on this website up-to-date and accurate, neither the State of North Dakota, nor any agency, officer, or employee of the State of North Dakota warrants the accuracy, reliability, or timeliness of any information published by this system, nor endorses any content, viewpoints, products, or services linked from this system, and shall not be held responsible for any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability, or timeliness of such information. Portions of such information may be incorrect or out of date. Any person or entity that relies on any information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk.
The State of North Dakota makes every effort to provide virus-free files but does not guarantee uncorrupted files.
CONTACT US
CONTACT US
If you have any questions about any of our policies, disclaimer, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us.
